Mi-chan,
みーちゃん、
Are you nervous?
緊 張してます?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
How old are you now?
今、いくつなんだっけ?
I'm 19 years old.
19歳です
student?
学生?
High school students.
高学生
Is school fun?
学校楽しいですか?
It's fun.
楽しいです
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏いるの?
I'm here.
います
How long have you been together?
どれくらい付き合ってる?
About half a year.
半年くらい
half a year.
半年
People at school?
学校の人?
that's right.
そうです
people at school.
学 校の人
A circle?
サークルとか?
Do you come across something like that?
そういうの出合うんですか?
At the moment.
今の時は
that's right.
そうです
Now is the time.
今の時
What kind of person is your type?
どういう人がタイプ?
What kind of person are you?
どういう人?
Someone to be with and feel at ease with.
一緒にいて、落ち着く人
Someone who is calm?
落ち着く人?
Anyway, is it okay if I'm not a good-looking guy?
別に、じゃあ、イケメンじゃなくても大丈夫?
Well, the face too...
まあ、顔も...
Is your face okay?
顔も大丈夫?
Personality too...
性格も...
Yeah.
うん
Yes, it's almost summer.
そう、そう、夏近いですけど
Do you want to go somewhere with your boyfriend?
彼氏と何かどっか行きたいとかなんですか?
sea.
海
I want to go to the beach.
海行きたいです
sea?
海?
It's going to burn, but is it okay?
焼けちゃうけど大丈夫ですか?
Well, it's just wearing long sleeves...
まあ、それはちょっと長袖着て...
Do you wear long sleeves?
長袖着る?
Wear long sleeves to avoid burning.
長袖着て、焼けないように
Do you want to go to Beekin or something?
ビーキンにとか行きたいですか?
I want to go.
行きたいです
I want to go to hot dai.
ホットダイに行きたいです
Then it's baked.
そしたら焼けます
I don't know her.
彼女知らないね
Is that so?
そうですかね
The style is nice too, after all.
スタイルもいいしさ、 や っぱ、
That's good.
いいよね
Swimsuit.
水着
Your boyfriend probably wants to see it too, right?
彼氏も見たいんじゃないですか?
What color would you like to go with?
何色の何か行きたいとかある?
light blue.
水色
light blue?
水色?
What do you want to do at the sea?
海って何したいんですか?
The sea...
海って...
I can't swim...
泳げはしないんで...
Can't you swim?
泳げないの?
I can't swim.
泳げないです
hammer?
金槌?
Do you know what a hammer is?
金槌ってわかる?
No, I don't know.
いや、わからない
A hammer...
金槌って...
I'm a person who can't swim...
泳 げない人で...
Will I drown if I go to the sea or pool?
海とかプールとか行ったら 溺れちゃう?
There is no escape in the sea.
海の中が逃げがってないんです
Can we go to the pool?
プールとか行ける?
You can swim in the pool, but...
プールは泳げるんですけど...
It would be great if there was a sandy beach...
砂浜とかあったら全然いいんですけど...
You don't know how deep the ocean is.
どんだけ深いかわからないよね、海なんてね
I don't know what it is.
何いるかわからない
Swim to your feet.
足元に泳ぐ
If you want to swim 25 meters, it's not at all.
25メートル泳ごうと思えば全然
Ah, I can probably go.
あ、多分行ける
Stamin.
スタミン
Then it's not a hammer.
じゃあ金槌じゃないね
Can't swim?
泳げない?
I can't swim in the sea.
海じゃ泳げない
So you don't want to get a sunburn?
じゃあ日焼けもしたくない?
I don't want to get a sunburn, but I want to wear a swimsuit.
日焼けはしたくないけど 水着は着たい
I want to wear a swimsuit and have fun.
水着着てはしゃぎたい
I want to have fun.
はしゃぎたい
I want to be surprised.
びっくりしたいですね
Something like filling it up.
なんかね、埋めたりとかね
Oh, I'd like to try that.
ああ、あれやってみたいですよね
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみですね
I bet your boyfriend is looking forward to it too.
彼氏も楽しみなんじゃないですかね、
Like this.
こんな
If only I had such a nice buddy.
こんなナイスバディだったら
It's good to see inside too.
見ていいんだよね、この中も
You can already see the bulge, you know.
膨らみがね、もう分かるもんね、もうね
It's sexy.
セクシーだしね
Your boyfriend will be happy about this too.
これは彼氏も喜ぶよね
It feels kind of solid after all, though.
やっぱなんかしっかりめな感じだけどね、
It's petite and cute.
小柄で可愛らしいですね
How tall are you now?
今、身長ってどれくらい?
It is 154.
154です
54?
It's 54.
54です
Ever since I was a student.
もうずっと、学生の時から
It's almost the same.
ほぼ変わらないでしょ
Has it changed?
変 わ ったか
It didn't grow at all.
全然、伸びなかったです
Didn't it grow?
伸びなかった?
It didn't grow.
伸びなかったです
Well then, I'd like you to go around the back a little more slowly.
じゃあ、後ろもちょっとゆっくり回ってもらって
Even if you look this way.
こっち向いても
Somehow, I knew I was just taking a picture from below.
なんか、今、下から撮ってたの分かってた
Yeah.
うん
Have you ever had your camera stolen?
なんか、盗撮とかされたことある?
Only once.
一回だけ
be?
ある?
Did you say anything about that?
それ、なんか言えたの?
Like, please stop.
止めてください、みたいな
I didn't say that.
言ってないです
Where?
どこで?
train?
電車?
It's a train, it's a train.
電車です、電車
Stairs?
階段とか?
I'm on the train.
電車の中です
On the train?
電車の中?
Were there many people?
人多かったの?
Not at all.
全然いないです
Were there not many people and you were turned away?
人多くなくて、遠ざされたの?
I think I probably did.
多分、してたなと思います
How did you shoot with the camera?
カメラ、どんな感じで撮ったの?
I feel like it's time to head over here.
なんか、もう、こっち向いてきな
I went out and did some kind of show.
出て、なんか、ショ
Then, keep facing the camera.
ット して、ずっとこっち、カメラ向いてきて
Were you being fucked like this?
こうやって下、やられてたの?
The picture below was taken in its entirety.
下、全体的に撮られたってことです
Opposite?
向かい側の?
yes.
はい
Maybe the one I'm in is short,
多分、私が入ってるあれが短くて、
It's all over the body.
全身にするって
Oh, I'm taking pictures.
あ、撮ってんなーって
I didn't say that.
言わなかったですけど
Couldn't you say it?
言えなかった?
I couldn't say it.
言えなかったです
On the other hand, I can't say that there are no people.
逆に、人いないと言えないね、なんかね
I don't think I can say either way.
どっちにしろ、言えない気がしますけど
It's scary, but.
怖いよね、でもね
Can I turn it over and show it to you?
めくって、自分から見せてもらってもいい?
Do you do this to your boyfriend?
彼氏にはこういうことするんですか?
do not.
しない
Have you never done it?
したことない?
Her underwear is also light blue.
下着も水色なんですね
I like it.
好きなんだ
what up?
どうした?
I'm kind of sweating.
なんか、汗かいてて
I was freaking out, right now.
びくってしたね、今ね
Sweat?
かいてる汗?
I'm writing.
かいてます
Do you sweat easily?
汗かきやすい?
No, when I get nervous.
いや、緊張すると
Not easy to write.
か きやすくない
I'm nervous.
緊張してるんだ
Over there, I got my hands on Betta.
そっちに、ベッタに手ついて
Just point your butt towards me.
お尻こっち向けてほら、そのまま
Face here
顔こっち
Can you see it?
見 える?
That's erotic.
エロいねー
I don't want to see it myself.
自分で見たくない
She's a good woman
いい女だね
ー.
ー
Touch the right.
右 触って
You're sweating.
汗かいてるねー
Hey, do you understand?
ちょっと、分かるよ?
this.
これ
real?
ほんと?
sweat.
汗
I'm sweating here.
ここに汗かくんだ
not at all.
全然
Sweaty?
汗かき?
No, I usually do that too.
いや、普段もしてる
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊 張してる
I'm sweating a lot.
すごい汗かいてる
This is it
これね
ー.
ー
Here too, even if I suddenly touch it,
ここ もさー、 急に触ってもね、
I was surprised.
びっくりしたね
Right now.
今ね
Does it get wet easily?
濡れやすい?
Maybe.
もしかして
It's easy to sweat and get wet easily.
汗かきやすいし、濡れやすいんだって
Oh, is that so?
あ、 そうなんですか?
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Here.
ここねー
Does it hurt a lot?
すごく痛い?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are your legs trembling?
足プルプルしてる?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It's hot.
熱いもんねー
a little bit.
ちょっと
It's hot, isn't it?
熱いよね
Well then, let's go to sleep.
じゃあ寝まおうか
Your breasts are big.
おっぱいおっきいねー
How many cups are there?
何カップあるんすか?
picture?
え?
Since when did that happen?
いつからそんなの?
Has it already ripened?
もう実ってた?
What about Brown?
ブラウンはいつつけど?
Okay, now.
いいよね、もうね
What did your boyfriend say?
彼氏、何て言ってた?
It's big, it's big.
でかい、でかいねーって
I said, ``No way.''
で かいねーって
This is huge, isn't it?
でかいよね、これねー
I don't know.
わかんないです
Don't you know?
わかんない?
It's me.
自分じゃ
I don't know.
わかんない
This is amazing.
すごいこれ
Once you see it, you'll want to touch it.
見たらもう触りたくなっちゃう
My hands are free.
勝手に手が
My underwear is see-through.
下着のの透けちゃってね
I'm starting to sweat a little.
ちょっと汗引いてきた
Well, yes.
まあ、はい
It's a bit hot, isn't it?
ちょっと熱いよね、もこもこがね
It's hot.
熱いです
I'm curious about this.
気になっちゃうな、これ
I'm shaking just by laughing.
笑っただけで揺れてるもん
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's jiggling.
ぷるんぷるんやねんからね
Use this broom.
こっちのほうきいんでね
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうですか?
Overflowing.
溢れんばかりの
surely.
確かに
This one is a little higher though.
こっちちょっと上あるけど
This is what's sticking out.
はみ出てるもん、こっち
This is what makes the veins stand out.
血管浮いてるのをやるよね、これ
hey.
ね
what up?
どう した?
no.
いや
I can't see anything.
なんも見えてないね
It's a little strange.
微妙だね
What's going on with this?
どうなってんの、これ
It's floating here.
浮いてきたね、こっちね
He was a bit shy and prickly.
ちょっと恥ずかしがりやなチクビしてたね
It started floating more and more.
どんどん浮いてきた
It's true.
ほんとだ
At first, it didn't show up at all.
最初ね、全然出てなかったのに
Why did you come out?
なんで出たんですか?
I don't know.
わかんないです
For the rest of my life
あと一生の日よく
Do you feel full?
ほ っぱいって感じる?
Chikubi.
チクビ
What will happen?
どうされるの?
It was touched normally.
普通に触られた
If you talk about chikubi for a moment, they'll stand up.
ちょっとチクビの話したら立ってるよね
feel?
感じる?
written on the back of the neck
首の後ろに書
Are you there?
いて る?
Are you writing that you have a lot today too?
お前今日もいっぱいって書いてる?
I'm writing.
書いてる
For the rest of my life
あと一生の日よく
Do you feel full?
ほ っぱいって感じる?
Chikubi.
チクビ
What will happen?
どうされるの?
It was touched normally.
普通に触られた
If you talk about chikubi for a moment, they'll stand up.
ちょっとチクビの話したら立ってるよね
feel?
感じる?
written on the back of the neck
首の後ろに書
Are you there?
いて る?
Are you writing that you have a lot today too?
お前今日もいっぱいって書いてる?
I'm writing.
書いてる
It feels good.
気分気持ちいいよね
Really listen to it.
耳をほんとに
Can you lick me?
舐められるの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Which chikubi do you feel more like?
どっちのチクビのほう感じるとこある?
About the same.
同じくらい
This one is a little more sharp.
こっちのほうピンピンだね
I had the bottom removed as well.
下も抜いてもらって
good?
いい?
It's wide, your body is big.
広 いね、体ね
What did they say?
どんなって言われてたの?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
Because it's coming out.
出るからって
Do you know why?
なんでか分かる?
Are you excited?
興奮してるの?
now.
今
What is this?
これ何?
Is this a store?
これ店かっけ?
this.
これ
What's going on?
どうなってんの?
this.
これ
What are you doing?
どうしてんの?
this.
これ
There's no hair here.
毛ないじゃん、ここ
In a room.
ある部屋で
I'm shaving here.
ここは剃ってる
Are you shaving?
剃ってるの?
Why did you shave?
なんで剃ったの?
why?
なんで?
Will it get stuffy?
むれちゃう?
Something...
なんか...
I don't want to shave.
剃りたくない
The base?
土台のほう?
picture?
え?
Should I fix it by hand?
手で直すの?
this.
これ
Show me.
見せてよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Just eyeliner?
アイラインだけ?
There isn't.
ないんだね
No?
だめ?
Here.
ここは
It might be wet.
濡れてるかも
Are you wet?
濡れてる?
I'd better check it out, then.
確認したほうがいいね、じゃあね
Better check.
確認したほうがいい
This is wet.
濡れてます、これ
It's wet.
濡れてますね
Oh my.
あらあら
A little butt...
ちょっとお尻...
Goo.
グーって
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
this.
これ
This is crazy.
びっちゃびちゃよ、これ
Oh, really?
え、本当に?
It's kind of cool...
なんかイッチな...
This is growing tremendously.
すごい伸びてる、これ
Is this going to get messy?
これ、ざれちゃう?
this.
これ
Right now, it's up to about my knees.
今ね、膝ぐらいまで伸びてる
Look at this.
見てみよ、これ
This is terrible.
やばいね、これね
Maybe I'll sit on the couch.
ソファに座ろうかもね
Spread it out wide.
いっぱい広げて
I have to check this out a bit.
ちょっと確認しないとだよ、これね
It's okay to lean back.
もたれちゃっていいや
Shall we go a little further back?
もうちょい後ろ行こうか
behind?
後ろ?
Yeah, step back and lean back.
うん、後ろに下がって、もたれて
Try expanding it yourself.
自分でこう、広げてみて
So that you can see inside.
中見えるように
Can you go from behind?
後ろから行ける?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's within what I can do.
できる範囲だよ
Would you like to touch this yourself?
これ自分で触ったりする?
Will you?
するの?
Why?
何で?
picture?
え?
Do you use toys or something?
なんかおもちゃとか使うの?
I've never used it.
使ったことないです
With your own fingers?
自分の指で?
When will you touch it?
いつ触るの?
when?
いつ?
When?
どういうとき?
Like before going to bed.
寝る前とか
It's easy to see because it's curved.
反ってるから見やすいんだからね
But it's also a little erotic that the butt part is still curved, isn't it?
でもちょっとお尻のところも反り残してるのもちょっとエロいね、
Around here.
この辺ね
Do you also put your fingers in it?
指も入れたりするの?
Don't put your fingers in it.
指は入れない
Just touch it?
触ったりするだけ?
Where do you touch it?
どこ触るの?
where?
どこ?
Yeah.
うん
It's because I'm painted,
これ自分が塗れてるからだからね、
It's slimy.
ヌルヌルしてるの
I don't know myself.
自分でわかんない
This is my naughty pond, this.
これ自分のエッチな池だよ、これ
It's so big, look.
すごいびっちゃびっちゃ、ほら
I'll put a lot of this on you.
いっぱいつけてあげるんだよ、これね
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
What do you feel the most here?
ここが一番感じる?
There's a mole in Piro Piro.
ぴろぴろに ほくろがあんだね
It's slippery and feels good, right?
ヌルヌルで気持ちいいでしょ?
Can I lick it?
舐 めていい?
Is it okay to lick it?
舐めるの大丈夫?
like?
好き?
Which one?
どっちどっち?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Oh no, no no.
やばい、やばい
It's kind of hard to breathe.
なんか息づらい
I was breathing, but it was getting rough.
息づかう、荒くなってたけど
I haven't been there.
行ってないね
no.
いや
picture?
え?
Have you been?
行ってた?
I couldn't resist.
我慢できなかったんだ
Puripururiuruuru.
ぷりぷりうるうる
My legs.
足が
It's a dream.
夢だよ
So, turn your back on me
それでさ、 裏背を立て
Runo.
る の
good?
いい?
Even if it's made of saliva
唾液でネルネルにしても
good?
いい?
For big feet.
ほ っぱい足に
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good, seriously.
気持ちいい、マジで
That's what I mean.
っていう
I don't know if it's perfect for my grandfather.
おじいちに完璧なわからない
My legs are shaking.
足が震える
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気 持ちいいね
It feels really good.
なんかめっちゃ気持ちいい
It's delicious there.
そこおいしもってる
My legs.
足が
Put your hand in front?
前に手をつける?
a little bit.
ちょっと
There
そこ
To.
に
What do you think?
全 然どう?
Do you understand?
わかる?
Tick-tock.
カチカチ
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
With one hand.
片手で
Just a little more.
もう ちょっと
It feels so good inside.
この奥めっちゃ気持ちいい
That's what makes it delicious.
そ こおいしくなってる
Put your hand in front?
前に手をつける?
a little bit.
ちょっと
What do you think?
全然どう?
Do you understand?
わかる?
Tick-tock.
カチカチ
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
home.
いえ
Ippa
い っぱ
I feel it.
い 感じてる
degree
ど
Does this feel good?
こ が気持ちいい?
Back?
奥?
Is it dangerous in the back?
奥やばい?
Is it slow?
ゆっくりやばい?
My legs are shaking.
足が震える
slowly.
ゆっくり
home.
いえ
Back?
奥?
Is it dangerous in the back?
奥やばい?
Should I make it sluggish?
だるだるにしたらいいのか
This is when I'm in a bit of a mood.
なんかイッチのときこれね
Because I moved to a tooth that felt good to me.
自分が気持ちいい歯に動いたから
A little bit in the back.
奥がちょっと
it hurts?
痛い?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It feels good, doesn't it?
気持ちいいんだよね
Is this it?
これしょ?
Not much.
あんまりね
It's soaking wet.
ビチョビチョだね
Here, here.
ここがね、ここ
It hurts, it hurts.
痛 い、痛い
I asked him to follow me.
後 ろついてもらったよ
I can see it inside.
入ってるとこ見えるよ
It moves by itself.
自分で動くんだよ
Would you like to leave it there?
置いてごらん?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Is it dangerous in the back?
奥やばい?
Back?
奥?
I thought about having her turn her butt.
お尻を向けてもらおうかと思った
picture?
え?
Should I move my butt back?
お尻をバックしようか
Look at me.
こっち向けて
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
Do you understand?
分 かる?
this.
これ
Look at Petan?
ペタンってついてごらん?
Get your hands on it.
手ついて
It feels good.
気 持ちいいね
terrible.
やばい
My stomach hurts.
お腹痛む
Is this dangerous?
これやばい?
It feels good in my stomach.
なんかのお腹の気持ちいいね
I was able to hold it in somehow.
なんか我慢できてた
Let's get comfortable together.
一緒に気持ちよくなろっか
Let's go, just like this.
行くよ、このまま
It's jiggling though.
プルプルしてるけど
My legs are terrible.
足やばいよ
My legs are shaking.
足が震えてる
Shall I stretch my stomach and sleep?
お腹を伸ばして寝ようか